

# Adrian Gorgos Frontend Developer

▶ https://portfolio-redesign-tau.vercel.app/ 🛗 23/09/1997 🏲 Romanian

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/gorgos-adrian/

## **Profile**

I am a **passionate** and **conscientious** player, with a proclivity for **meeting deadlines**. I'd like to work for a company that promotes best practices and offers a variety of customer projects. Committed to high web design, user experience, usability, and speed for a diverse range of endusers.

## **Skills**

#### **Tech Stack**

Agile, Bootstrap, GIT, HTML5/CSS3, SASS, Javascript, TailwindCSS, React.js, Next.js, Framer Motion

### **Apps and Tools**

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Figma, Docker, Slack

## **Professional Experience**

09/2021 - present

#### **Worked On Portoflio**

I have created my portfolio based on an online design I found on Figma. The website is Statically Generated and built with Next.js, which in comparison with React increases the page loading speed and adds additional SEO features.

During this project I have worked with:

- Framer Motion is a really cool library for React.js which allows creating animations at ease.
- TailwindCSS for basic CSS styling. This utility-first library allows me to create UI components extremely fast with an eye for accessibility.
- Additionally, I have used React-Intersection-Observer to trigger the animations on scroll.
- · Firestore for the contact form.
- Swiperis for the implementation of the carousel

06/2021 – present	Worked On Other Minimal Websites I have worked on other miscellaneous websites, which can be found in my portfolio section. I have styled them mainly using Bootstrap.
11/2019 – 12/2019 Craiova, Romania	Worked On Redesigning The Website of My University in Craiova During my studies at the university, I engaged in redesigning the website for my studying department: https://litere.ucv.ro/litere/ ☑ where I practiced the basic layout of the websites.
Courses	
07/2021 – present	Responsive Web Design, freeCodeCamp
2021 – 2021	Next.js Tutorial, Codevolution
2021 – 2021	React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux), Academind by Maximilian Schwarzmüller
2021 – 2021	Next.js Tutorial For Beginners, The Net Ninja
2021 – 2021	Learn React for Free, Learn Javascript for Free, Scrimba
2021 – 2021	React.js Tutorial, Dave Gray
2021 – 2021	Advanced Javascript Concepts, Dave Gray
2021 – 2021	React Tutorial - Fundamentals, Hooks, Context API, React Router, Custom Hooks, Codding Addict
Languages	
English	• • • • • Russian
Romanian	• • • •
Education	
2016 – 2019 Craiova, Romania	Bachelor Degree in Applied Visual Communication, University of Craiova During the 3 years of study, I had the chance to participate in various design internships where I used Illustrator and After Effects for creating media content
Interests	
GraphQL Gatsby	Node.js PHP Three.js Docker